iSpring fans in this installment of
iSpring粉丝在本期的
spring tips we're gonna look at the
春天的技巧，我们要看看
different options for working with
使用的不同选择
servlet containers with a spring boot
带有弹簧启动的servlet容器
application or from a spoon springboard
应用或从勺子跳板
application this includes of course the
应用程序当然包括
embedded containers that Springwood
斯普林伍德的嵌入式容器
supports out of the box for example the
支持开箱即用
red head under to a project the Eclipse
红头下一个项目到Eclipse
jetty project and the apache tomcat
码头项目和Apache Tomcat
project and then we're also gonna look
项目，然后我们还要看
at how spring boot based applications
基于Spring Boot的应用程序
can be deployed into a servlet container
可以部署到servlet容器中
now I want to distinguish all of the
现在我想区分所有
support from the support in other web
来自其他网站的支持
runtimes for example that of spring 5
例如Spring 5的运行时
which is due this summer for a reactive
这是由于今年夏天的反应
neti based rent I'm and that's support
基于neti的租金，这就是支持
for example that you might find in in
例如，您可能会在
the Play Framework which is also not
Play框架
based on the servlets sort of
基于servlet的
specification so this in this discussion
规范，因此在此讨论中
we're going to focus our look at service
我们将专注于服务
in particular we're going to talk about
特别是我们要谈论的是
options for manipulating the embedded
操作嵌入式的选项
containers and then we're going to talk
容器，然后我们要谈谈
about options for integrating with you
关于与您整合的选项
know a standalone sort of container or
知道一个独立的容器或
any or really any Java EE application
任何或实际上任何Java EE应用程序
server by extension right so we're gonna
通过扩展正确的服务器，所以我们要
build you application we'll just call it
建立您的应用程序，我们将其称为
our demo application or whatever you
我们的演示应用程序或任何您
call it we call it servlet demo and when
称它为servlet demo以及何时
we bring in Springs for for building web
我们引进Springs建立网站
applications and we'll build a simple
应用程序，我们将构建一个简单的
resting point just something with which
休息点
would which with which we can work and
我们可以与之合作的
you know one thing that I've done here
你知道我在这里做的一件事
is that I've left the default settings
是我保留了默认设置
here I've left the default settings for
在这里，我保留了默认设置
for the application as a as a dot jar
作为点罐应用
now I could have elected to choose to
现在我可以选择选择
dot war but will turn this dot jar into
点战争，但会将这个点罐变成
a dot war later on and we'll see that
一场点战之后，我们将看到
there's some benefits and in doing so
有一些好处，这样做
okay now I've got an application up and
好吧，现在我已经有了一个应用程序，
running let's modify our code quite a
运行我们来修改我们的代码
simple rest controller so we'll say
简单的休息控制器，所以我们会说
class greetings
上课问候
rest controller okay at rest controller
休息控制器可以休息控制器
at get mapping greetings and I will say
在获得映射问候时，我会说
map of string string greetings
字符串问候语映射
when we turn a empty collection so
当我们打开一个空集合时
greeting
问候
hello world it's not an introduction
你好世界，这不是介绍
it's a almost empty collection it's
这是一个几乎是空的收藏
gonna have one attribute this can be
会有一个属性，可以是
turned into a JSON map so if we if we
变成了JSON映射，所以如果我们
run this application just run the
运行此应用程序，只需运行
application on a local machine we should
在本地计算机上的应用程序，我们应该
see that spin up on port 8080 by default
看到默认情况下在端口8080上旋转
and the reason for that is because of
那是因为
course spring boot is embedding Apache
当然，Spring Boot嵌入了Apache
Tomcat by default when you bring in the
当您引入Tomcat时，默认情况下
web support did I give it a mapping
网络支持我给它做了一个映射
greetings
问候
when you spring when spring boot starts
当你春天时，弹簧启动开始
up it but if all to embed the Apache
起来，但要是全部嵌入到Apache中
Tomcat servlet container until we get a
Tomcat servlet容器，直到我们得到一个
wet working web server available for us
湿工作网络服务器对我们可用
out of the box now this is a servlet
开箱即用，这是一个servlet
container right so you can do all manner
正确的容器，所以您可以做所有的事情
of different things that you would do in
在不同的事情上
a server container using Tomcat right
使用Tomcat的服务器容器权利
this is a servlet container here right
这是一个servlet容器
and and ultimately what spring boot is
最终是什么 spring boot
doing is it's Auto configuring the
这样做是自动配置
spring MVC dispatcher servlet and
Spring MVC调度程序servlet和
framework servlet and so on for you
框架servlet等为您服务
right all that stuff gets done for you
对，所有事情都为您完成
behind the scenes and the way we're
幕后以及我们的方式
doing this is that we're embedding
这样做是因为我们正在嵌入
Tomcat and then we're using the
Tomcat，然后我们使用
programmatic capability of the servlet
Servlet的编程能力
through that one specification to
通过那个规范来
programmatically configure all the
以编程方式配置所有
relevant objects that you know the
您知道的相关对象
infrastructure the apparatus that spring
基础设施
needs to be an effective web framework
需要成为一个有效的网络框架
on top of the servlet engine you can
在servlet引擎之上，您可以
participate in all that right spring
参加所有的春天
give you a chance to participate now
让您现在有机会参加
that you can register filters and and
您可以注册过滤器和
and servlets as well you can register
和servlet以及您可以注册
custom things that should be registered
应注册的自定义内容
with a servlet container so let's
与一个servlet容器一起，让我们
suppose I wanted to build a custom
假设我想建立一个自定义
filter right I can say component class
过滤器正确，我可以说组件类
my custom filter implements filter and
我的自定义过滤器实现了filter和
this is a Java servlet Jobbik servlet
这是一个Java servlet Jobbik servlet
filter right I mean you know traditional
过滤器正确，我是说你知道传统
kind of thing import that whoops wrong
那种错误的东西进口
one
一
Java code filter okay and we're gonna
Java代码过滤器还可以，我们要
override three methods here the CIA
在中情局中覆盖三种方法
methods and we have just three methods
方法，我们只有三种方法
here let's go ahead and log you know as
在这里，让我们继续并记录您的身份
a proof of the pudding let's create a
布丁的证明让我们创建一个
log and we'll just log each method in
记录，我们只记录每个方法
there see any other parameters okay so
那里看到其他参数了吗
this log got info in it and they're just
这个日志中有信息，他们只是
a config okay
配置好
and we want to another log method here
我们想在这里使用另一种日志方法
saying that we've received the request
说我们已经收到了请求
new filter servlet request a servlet
新的过滤器servlet请求一个servlet
response and I won't register the I
回应，我不会注册
won't log the filter chain but I will
不会记录过滤链，但我会
call the proceed method right this is
调用proce方法正确，这是
the contract of the servlet API is to
Servlet API的合同是
call the filter chain after you've done
完成后调用过滤器链
something after you pre-process that
预处理后的东西
request so every request that comes in
要求，所以每一个要求
to the application will get routed
到应用程序将被路由
through all the so all the filters are
通过所有的过滤器
that apply and that are applicable and
适用和适用的
in this case the the filter will get a
在这种情况下，过滤器将获得
chance to do something and then hand it
有机会做某事然后递给它
to the next filter in the chain if there
到链中的下一个过滤器
is a chain until finally one also log do
是一条链，直到最后一个也要登录
destroy method right so destroy very
正确的销毁方法，所以销毁非常
good if we restart this this is already
好，如果我们重新启动它，这已经是
enough we can already see the results
我们已经可以看到结果了
just by registering of component right
仅通过注册组件权利
we're in habit we don't have to talk to
我们有习惯，我们不必交谈
the servlet container we don't have to
不需要的servlet容器
do anything particular we just have to
做任何特别的事情，我们只需要
declare a spring bean of the right type
声明正确类型的spring bean
and it gets automatically plugged in to
它会自动插入
the request so we can see my custom
该请求，以便我们可以看到我的自定义
filter in it is already in place there's
过滤器已经到位了
the application filter config we can see
我们可以看到的应用程序过滤器配置
the details of that let's go ahead and
细节，让我们继续
make a request to our application
向我们的申请提出要求
endpoint here a few these I'm just
终结点这里我只是这些
hitting command R and you can see that
点击命令R，您可以看到
as that happens it says do filter and
发生这种情况时，它说做过滤器和
then it shows us the requests facade the
然后它向我们显示了请求的外观
requests are the response beside
请求是旁边的响应
etcetera these are the
这些是
httpservletrequest in response subtypes
响应子类型中的httpservletrequest
that Tomcat and the passing into our
Tomcat和传递到我们的
method on that request so or do we get
该方法的要求还是我们得到
the benefits of the filter API now a
过滤器API的优势现在
filter usually has some sort of sense of
过滤器通常具有某种意义上的
ordering right some sort of priority and
优先订购某种优先级
similarly you know you may want to
同样，您知道您可能想要
configure other things besides the
配置除
actual type itself and so for this you
实际类型本身，所以为此
can do you can register what's called a
你可以注册所谓的
servlet registration beam or a filter
servlet注册光束或过滤器
registration so here's a filter
注册，这是一个过滤器
registration beam and in this case I'm
对准光束，在这种情况下，我是
gonna return a filter registration beam
会返回过滤器对准光束
new filter registration meaning I'm
新的过滤器注册意味着我
gonna make it so that this filters not a
要做到这一点，以便该过滤器不会
spring me and I'm gonna instantiate it
让我春天，我将实例化它
myself right my custom filter plug that
我自己对我的自定义过滤器插头
into the pipeline here and I'm gonna say
进入这里的管道，我要说
my custom filter and I can specify all
我的自定义过滤器，我可以指定所有
manner of other things here I can say
我可以在这里说其他方式
you know I can add initialization
你知道我可以添加初始化
parameters
参数
and URL pattern parameters I can say
和URL模式参数我可以说
whether it's a synchronous or not I can
无论是同步还是不可以
you know I can specify all the things
你知道我可以指定所有东西
that you would expect to specify when
您希望指定何时
programmatically registering a filter
以编程方式注册过滤器
using the servlet 3.1 API including the
使用Servlet 3.1 API，包括
order right so you can specify that as
订购权，因此您可以将其指定为
well you can also get some of that
好吧，你也可以得到一些
effect you can also get the ordering
效果还可以下单
just by using at ordered right if you
只是通过按顺序使用权利，如果你
just uh there you go
只是你去那里
I'd order right so if you specify a
我会正确点菜，所以如果您指定一个
number there on the under component and
在底部组件上编号
leave it at a component then you don't
把它留在一个组件上，那么你就不会
need this so you don't need to filter
需要这个，所以你不需要过滤
registration beam to get ordering in a
配准光束以订购
spring command it's bring context but
春天的命令，它带来了上下文，但
but everything else you you know if you
但是你知道的其他一切，如果你
want to specify all that other stuff you
想要指定所有其他东西
have to do so on the filter registration
必须在过滤器注册上这样做
beam in our case it doesn't really buy
在我们的情况下，它不是真的买
us anything to configure anything else
我们可以配置其他任何东西
I'll just leave it as is and we start so
我将其保持原样，我们开始
we can confirm everything it's it's
我们可以确认所有的一切
still working as expected now again it's
仍然按预期工作，现在
worth understanding it there's also a
值得了解的还有一个
servlet registration b9 servlet
servlet注册b9 servlet
registration beam and servlet
配准束和servlet
registration beans are great if you want
如果您愿意，注册豆很棒
to register a servlet any servlet right
注册servlet的任何servlet权限
uh some loops that you are used to using
呃，你习惯使用的一些循环
maybe you're using something it isn't
也许您使用的不是
managed by the spring framework for you
由spring框架为您管理
already and the nice thing about this is
已经，这件事的好处是
that you can put these beams in on auto
您可以将这些光束自动
configuration so you can actually do
配置，因此您实际上可以做
very dynamic things you can do if you
您可以做的非常有活力的事情
put them in an auto configuration class
将它们放在自动配置类中
that is to say a class that is a new
也就是说，这是一个新的课程
that is enumerated in the spring that
在春天列举
factories entry under the auto
汽车下厂入门
configuration for example here it says
例如配置在这里说
at enable auto configuration and then it
在启用自动配置，然后
shows a list of Java classes if your
显示Java类列表，如果您的
driver configuration class Liz lives in
驱动程序配置类Liz居住在
them and in that enumeration it'll
他们，并在该枚举
respond to the conditional annotations
响应条件注释
so you can register or Matt men are
这样您就可以注册，或者Matt男子是
different things based on dynamic sort
基于动态排序的不同事物
of tests that are provided for you out
为您提供的测试
of the box of course we've got some very
当然，我们有一些非常
useful conditions out of the box here as
开箱即用的有用条件
well but you know if you want to use
好吧，但您知道是否要使用
some of the other ones you can write
其他一些你可以写的
your own condition with a conditional
你自己的条件和条件
rotation okay so that's that's how you
旋转好吧，那就是你的方式
register custom filters and strobe it
注册自定义过滤器并对其进行选通
and you can take advantage of the lower
您可以利用较低的
sort of machinery inside the servlet
Servlet内部的某种机械
container without having to deploy to a
容器而无需部署到
standard server container you may want
您可能需要的标准服务器容器
to configure things for the servlet
为servlet配置事物
container and there's a
容器，有一个
watch of properties are well supported
监视属性得到很好的支持
across all the different embedded
跨越所有不同的嵌入式
container options so for example I can
容器选项，例如，我可以
specify the port right serve it up port
指定端口权为其服务端口
equals 80 10 right I can also specify
等于80 10对，我也可以指定
things like SSL so I can say server SSL
SSL之类的东西，所以我可以说服务器SSL
and I pass in the the key store the
然后我将密钥库
trust or the the you know whether should
信任还是你知道是否应该
be enabled or not you know all that kind
被启用还是不知道
of stuff and this works in a consistent
的东西，这在一个一致的作品
way across Tomcat and and jetty and
跨越Tomcat和码头
undertow I can also specify compression
我还可以指定压缩
gzip compression in particular right so
gzip压缩特别正确，所以
I can say okay let's enable it true and
我可以说好吧，让我们启用它，
let's point it to anything that responds
让我们将其指向任何可以响应的内容
with application in JSON so this is a
与JSON中的应用程序，所以这是一个
comma delimited list of mime types that
以逗号分隔的mime类型列表
are supposed to being compressed and so
应该被压缩等等
with that in place I can restart the
有了这个我可以重新启动
application having done nothing else and
应用程序什么也没做
now if I make a request by default with
现在，如果我默认发出以下请求
curl I'm gonna make a request without
卷曲，我会不带要求
the content without the except encoding
没有除编码以外的内容
there right I'll make a request like
在那里，我会发出类似的请求
this get rid of that first and you can
首先摆脱它，你可以
see that it failed because I called the
看到它失败了，因为我打电话给了
wrong endpoint on the wrong port some
错误端口上的错误端点
readings maybe 10 and it shows us hello
读数可能是10，它向我们显示了你好
world and there's a result and in the
世界，有结果，在
response the content type is application
响应内容类型为application
Jason it is not in not compressed just
杰森不是在没有压缩只是
yet so now let's revisit this and bring
但现在让我们重新回顾一下并带来
in the correct header there the correct
在正确的标题中有正确的
header and the correct port in the
标头和正确的端口
correct uh endpoint so I'll say content
正确的端点，所以我会说内容
I'm gonna say that I'm gonna accept an
我要说我要接受
encoding of type gzip and that I want to
我想要的gzip类型的编码
call that endpoint and when I do I get
叫那个端点，我什么时候得到
binary data back this is compressed data
二进制数据返回这是压缩数据
now this is this is more efficient
现在这是更有效的
obviously in this particular case where
显然在这种情况下
I'm returning all of you know lesser
我回传给你们所有的人
tweets worth of characters it may not be
推文值得的字符可能不是
that important but if I were to return a
那很重要，但是如果我要返回一个
substantial amount of JSON this could be
大量的JSON可能是
a very valuable thing browsers will
浏览器会做的一件非常有价值的事情
automatically decode that for you and
自动为您解码并
this K this kind of compression can be
这种K压缩可以是
super useful especially apart for static
超级有用，尤其是对于静态而言
of resources things like CSS files and
资源，例如CSS文件和
an image isn't alright well maybe more
图像不好，也许更多
so JavaScript and CSS but either way you
因此使用JavaScript和CSS，但无论哪种方式
get a lot of benefit from an
从中得到很多好处
enabling compression gzip compression in
启用压缩gzip压缩
your application and spring boot makes
您的应用程序和Spring Boot使
it dead simple to do so so you can
这样做很简单，所以您可以
specify for all manner of different
指定各种不同的方式
things that you want to compress them or
您想要压缩它们的东西，或者
not compress them you can also say I
不压缩它们，你也可以说我
want my resource chain the thing that's
希望我的资源链是
serving up things in your source main
在源主中提供服务
resources directory
资源目录
things like your JavaScript files in
诸如JavaScript文件之类的东西
your your your CSS files and so on
您的CSS文件等等
those resources that are going to be
那些将是
piped directly to the client or perhaps
直接通过管道传输到客户端，或者
even served from a CDN in an alternate
甚至还可以从CDN投放
case those can be gzip compressed as
那些可以被gzip压缩为
well so if you have things that are
好吧，如果你有东西
bought that are not volatile they're not
买的不是不稳定的，不是
going to change a lot and they're heavy
会发生很大变化，而且很沉重
they're fat and a lot of a lot of the
他们很胖，很多
poorest as JSON for example in CSS and
最差的JSON，例如CSS和
JavaScript tend to be this is an ideal
JavaScript往往是一个理想的选择
sort of option there okay now sometimes
现在有些选择还可以
it's nice to be able to configure engine
能够配置引擎很好
or embedded server container specific
或特定于嵌入式服务器容器的
features and I've we've got properties
功能，我有属性
that expose a lot of that for you as
为您暴露了很多
well right so there's server dot Tomcat
很好，所以有服务器点Tomcat
right servin up Tomcat tot asterisk so
正确服务Tomcat tot星号
for example the header I wanna the the
例如我想要的标题
header that I want exposed when I'm
我要公开的标题
doing a forward for example the number
做一个转发，例如号码
of threads I want the maximum number of
我想要最大数量的线程
threads and the work of pool the max
线程和最大池工作
number of connections I want to accept
我要接受的连接数
the base directory how many processors I
基本目录我有多少个处理器
want the background the access log
希望后台访问日志
configuration I mean really just any can
配置，我的意思是实际上任何都可以
anything you want you can imagine
您想得到的任何东西
specifying most of that is here right we
指定大部分是在这里，我们
where we cannot do a specific or we
我们不能做具体的事情，或者我们
cannot do a general purpose
不能通用
configuration property like serving a
配置属性，例如
port or the SSL or compression or
端口或SSL或压缩或
something like that there are sometimes
像这样的东西有时
you know container specific properties
您知道容器的特定属性
and that applies equally for undertow
这同样适用于拖曳
here are some access log configuration
这是一些访问日志配置
options and you know your i/o threads
选项，并且您知道您的I / O线程
and how many worker threads you want and
以及您想要多少个工作线程
same for jetty right so here as well JD
码头也一样，这里还有JD
how many within without the largest post
没有最大职位的情况下有多少人
size that seems to be common across all
似乎在所有情况下都通用的尺寸
three of them the number of incoming
其中三个传入的数量
acceptor threads and that's a common
受体线程，这是常见的
I'll be a different named property
我将成为另一个命名的财产
across at least Tomcat and jetty see a
至少跨越Tomcat和码头
blob object right you can you can
Blob对象可以，您可以
configure these things at will but
随意配置这些东西，但是
sometimes it's useful to be able to
有时能够
interact with the container
与容器互动
programmatically right here we're just
以编程方式在这里，我们只是
specifying properties and you can get
指定属性，您可以获得
some done
一些完成
by putting some one set of properties in
通过放置一些属性
a different property file and using a
不同的属性文件并使用
profile so you know application
个人资料，以便您了解应用程序
- jetty would be a set of configuration
-码头将是一套配置
that would represent a set of configure
代表一组配置
configuration properties that apply only
仅适用的配置属性
when you're when you've activated the
当您激活了
jetty profile and you could presumably
码头概况，你大概可以
only do that when you're running an
仅在您运行
application named jetty but it's nice to
名为jetty的应用程序，但对
be able to programmatically interact
能够以编程方式进行交互
with these things as well so spring boot
还有这些东西，所以 spring boot
features a number of very convenient
功能很多，很方便
callbacks the most useful which from my
回调最有用的
money is the embedded servlet container
money是嵌入式servlet容器
customizer so here we're gonna say my
定制器，所以在这里我们要说我的
customizer implements embedded container
定制程序实现嵌入式容器
[Music]
[音乐]
customizer right and this is a regular
定制器的权利，这是一个常规
spring mean as anything else so we just
春天意味着什么，所以我们只是
override that method there and we get a
在那里重写该方法，我们得到一个
chance here to interact with the
有机会与
container here we can set a lot of the
容器在这里我们可以设置很多
properties that we saw set in the and
我们在和中看到的属性
the application of properties things
属性事物的应用
like the compression right there's the
像压缩一样，
compression support so you pass in a new
压缩支持，以便您传递新的
compression object with the appropriate
适当压缩对象
configurations or the context path again
再次配置或上下文路径
this is exactly this is something you
这就是你
can specify right here context context
可以在这里指定上下文上下文
pack right there it is right that would
打包在那里，这是正确的
be that that this turns into a call to
是因为这变成了对
this right so the common things are here
这样的权利，所以常见的事情在这里
exposed as a centers on this
以此为中心公开
configurable admitted stroller container
可配置的收纳婴儿车容器
that said sometimes it's useful to as we
那说有时候对我们很有用
say downcast and to manipulate specific
说沮丧，并操纵具体
features of the underlying container so
基础容器的功能如此
if Tomcat embedded servlet container
如果Tomcat嵌入了servlet容器
factory that class is assignable from
可从中分配该类的工厂
container not to give class then Sadler
容器不给课，然后萨德勒
I 1tc casting it passing another
我1TC铸造它通过另一个
container is that the right type in it
容器是其中正确的类型
look at the subtypes its Tomcat embedded
看一下它的Tomcat嵌入的子类型
servlet container Factory yes it is so
servlet容器工厂是的
if if it's assignable to that then this
如果它可以分配给这个
will this will work anyway and I can say
这将无论如何都会起作用，我可以说
a log dot cut a log here
日志点在此处剪切日志
long back great log okay
早就回来了，很好的日志
log tech info is Tomcat okay so we're in
记录技术信息是Tomcat可以，所以我们进入了
Tomcat and we can do specific things
Tomcat，我们可以做一些特定的事情
there as well using the downcast type so
还有使用向下转换类型
here we can get access to the collection
在这里我们可以访问集合
of connector customizers right these are
的连接器定制程序是这些
the things that actually respond to
实际反应的事物
requests in the actual underlying tomcat
实际底层tomcat中的请求
engine we can get access to the context
引擎，我们可以访问上下文
customizers and so a lot of the features
定制器等很多功能
that we do support for you we we expose
我们为您提供支持，我们向您展示
as implementations of these two
作为这两个的实现
interfaces that we plug into this
我们插入的接口
collection for you and you can do the
为您收藏，您可以
same thing if you have something you
如果你有东西，你也是一样
want to add that isn't already well
要补充一点，那就不是很好
supported out-of-the-box then this is an
受支持的开箱即用
ideal place to you know plugging in
您知道插入的理想场所
implementations of either one of these
这些之一的实现
types of beans is probably your best
最好的豆子类型
your best bet now there's other
现在最好的选择是
properties here as well you can get the
这里的属性，你也可以得到
valves you can get the you are encoding
阀门可以得到您正在编码的
you can get the base directory you can
您可以获得基本目录
set the protocol you can set bowels you
设置协议可以设置肠子
can do all sorts of sort of low-level
可以做各种各样的低级
stuff this is this this corresponds more
东西，这是这个，这对应更多
or less to the configuration that you'd
或更少的配置
set up in and the Tomcat - you know
在Tomcat中设置-您知道
Catalina configuration XML at this point
此时的Catalina配置XML
now you're dealing with the very
现在你正在处理
specific implementation details of the
具体实施细节
container and hopefully you haven't had
容器，希望您还没有
to do that hopefully you don't need to
希望这样做，您不需要
do that but it's nice to know that you
做到这一点，但是很高兴认识你
can the same is true for the other ones
其他人也一样吗
right so if undertow embedded server
正确，因此如果嵌入式嵌入式服务器
container factory that class that is
集装箱工厂那类是
assignable from container class then we
可从容器类分配，然后我们
assign that so okay class dot cast
分配好点的班级点播
passing in the container and there we
通过容器，在那里
are so undertow dot you know add build
这么点点，你知道添加构建
customizers add and mother this is
定制者添加，妈妈这是
another customizer option this is not
另一个定制器选项不是
native so natively supported by Tomcat
本机如此受Tomcat本地支持
or under tow these customizers are
或拖曳这些定制器是
Spring Buddhism right - what you're
春季佛教对-您是什么
using here what you're plugging in are
使用这里您要插入的是
these customizers that get plugged into
这些插入的定制器
the the creation of the container so you
容器的创建，以便您
don't have to override the creation you
不必覆盖您的创作
can just plug into certain parts of the
可以插入到
of the container again this is keeping
的容器再次保持
with the idea that spring at the end of
想到春天结束
the day is a framework it's it
今天是一个框架
implements the open-closed principle
实行开闭原则
it's open for extension you can change
它是开放的，您可以更改
the run
运行
behavior of the application without
没有该应用程序的行为
having to actually change spring itself
必须实际改变弹簧本身
right uh although you can since it's
是的，虽然你可以，但是
open source so hello Dutch info is
开源，所以你好荷兰信息是
undertow okay and let's do the last one
知道了，让我们做最后一个
jetty embedded server container factory
码头嵌入式服务器容器厂
that class dot is assignable from
该类点可从
container good class and we just do the
容器良好的课程，我们只是做
same thing again jetty dot class
同样的事情码头点类
typecast container very good log that
类型转换容器非常好的日志
info is jetty very good very good so
信息很好，很好，所以
there there we have all three of them
在那里，我们所有三个人
now let's go see in what that looks like
现在我们来看一下
well I'm let's go ahead and run it what
好吧，让我们继续并运行它
should see is tomcat ring true right
应该看到的是tomcat ring正确吗
this should be the one and only
这应该是唯一的
expression that mana that works here and
表示在这里起作用的法术力和
that's only after we've successfully
只有在我们成功之后
signed the container to that type right
正确地将该容器签名
so is Tomcat there we are so that worked
Tomcat也在那里，所以工作了
we are indeed in a tomcat application
我们确实在使用tomcat
now you may be wondering how we can
现在您可能想知道我们如何
change that right as I said the default
如我所说的更改默认权限
behavior the default configuration for a
行为的默认配置
spring good application when you bring
带上时春季很好的应用
in spring boots start a web is to also
在 spring boot 开始一个网站是也
in turn bring in spring boot starter
依次带来spring boot启动器
Tomcat you may not want to use Tomcat
您可能不想使用Tomcat的Tomcat
that's fair enough yeah you might have
足够公平，是的，你可能有
some application that needs some other
一些需要其他应用程序
specific feature you know whatever you
您知道的特定功能
want right we're not trying to to twist
想要正确，我们不试图扭曲
your arm here so spring boot starter
你的手臂在这里，所以弹簧启动启动器
tomcat will make that provided that
tomcat将做到这一点，前提是
means to say that is to say we're gonna
意思是说我们要
exclude this from the runtime footprint
从运行时足迹中排除
of the app of the bundled application it
捆绑应用程序的应用程序
won't be available when you do maven
做Maven时将不可用
dependency tree on the resulting
结果的依赖树
artifact it won't be available rather in
神器，它将不再可用
the in the compiled artifacts jars right
在已编译的工件罐中
and there were in the Lib directory if
并且在Lib目录中，如果
you well now we need to replace it with
您好，我们现在需要替换为
some other embedded server sort of
其他一些嵌入式服务器
implementation so let's bring in spring
实施，让我们进入春季
boot starter Jenny okay all I'm doing is
开机启动器珍妮，好吧，我要做的就是
going to bring in jetty excluded after a
打算在一个
fact the the tomcat support and if we do
其实tomcat的支持，如果我们这样做
this correctly assuming I don't have any
正确地假设我没有任何东西
specific Tomcat specific code this won't
特定的Tomcat特定代码，这不会
be true anymore JD will be true so let's
JD将成为真实，所以让我们
see
看到
that should be okay yeah let's go and we
没关系，我们走吧，我们
are so now if we look at the application
现在，如果我们看一下应用程序
the application has started up on port
该应用程序已在端口上启动
80 10 it's here available for us it's an
80 10这对我们来说是可用的
ingnieur embedded Cyrillic container
ingénieur嵌入式西里尔文容器
all the same things work so there we are
所有相同的东西都起作用，所以我们在那里
if I called greetings with the
如果我打电话给
accept-encoding I get the result as we
接受编码我得到的结果
expect let's go ahead and remove the
期待我们继续删除
accept-encoding header and get the the
接受编码标头并获取
raw JSON so again that's supported
原始JSON，因此再次受支持
correctly across the different
正确地跨越不同
implementations and and so on so I can
实现等等，这样我就可以
do the same thing for undertow replacing
做相同的事情替换
jetty with undertow and restarting and
拖曳并重新启动码头
there's our application I didn't give
有我没有给我们的申请
enough time to restart I think and
我认为有足够的时间重新启动
didn't give my idea enough time to
没有给我足够的时间
refresh its catalogue of the classpath
刷新其类路径的目录
libraries there we are under to embed
我们要嵌入的库
it's from a container so we've now
是从一个容器里来的，所以我们现在
switched across these different
在这些不同的地方切换
implementations we've looked at how to
我们已经研究了如何实现
work with the the underlying types and
使用基础类型和
again you can do you can take advantage
再次，你可以做，你可以利用
of all the different features of these
这些的所有不同特征
containers by by using those um those
通过使用那些容器
customizers right so one thing that's
定制器是正确的，这是一件事
you know kind of a common ask is how
你知道一个常见的问题是
would I bind something in jndi well by
我可以通过jndi绑定一些东西吗
default Tomcat doesn't use Jan yeah but
默认的Tomcat不使用Jan是的，但是
if you want to stand up at JDI context
如果您想站在JDI上下文中
and bind a bean to it and then make that
并绑定一个bean到它，然后使
available as a as a context reference to
可用作上下文参考
your application you can do that in for
您的应用程序可以在
example a one of these customizers or
例如这些定制器之一，或
you could register your own embedded
您可以注册自己的嵌入式
servlet container factory B I have two
servlet容器工厂BI有两个
can register your own Tomcat in bed sort
可以在床上整理自己的Tomcat
of container Factory and override the
容器Factory的值并覆盖
relevant callbacks right and we spring
正确的回调，我们春天
butjust provides these beans by default
butjust默认提供这些bean
and then it passes into the passes them
然后它传递到传递
into the customizers but you could
进入定制器，但您可以
provide own bean like this right and
像这样提供自己的豆
here you can override whatever you want
在这里您可以覆盖任何您想要的
you can override the post process
您可以覆盖发布过程
context to configure context a configure
上下文配置上下文配置
access else tour provider you can
访问其他旅游提供商，您可以
override all these different sort of
覆盖所有这些不同类型的
callbacks all these are sort of
所有这些回调
lifecycle hooks that Springwood exposes
Springwood公开的生命周期挂钩
for you when it remembers this
当你想起这个
application so you can do things like
应用程序，因此您可以执行以下操作
exposing things in Jan di
在扬迪揭露事物
configuring other connectors that are
配置其他连接器
automatically supportive view by spring
春季自动支持视图
mood now once you've done that you may
一旦完成，现在就可以
decide okay well I've got this
决定好吧，我有这个
application I want to turn it into a dot
我想把它变成一个点的应用程序
water application and you know there's
浇水，你知道
some value and turning it into a dot
一些价值并将其变成一个点
waar even if you're not going to deploy
即使您不打算部署
necessarily to a servlet container you
一定要一个servlet容器
can turn it into a dot waar with the
可以将它变成点点
with you know to keep in mind that it
与您知道要记住的是
may be deployed to a server container
可能部署到服务器容器
and so as an example let's we've got
举个例子，让我们
this at undertow let's leave it there
这个在underwow让我们留在那里
let's turn this into our wire you can
让我们把它变成我们的电线
still have executable wires right yeah
仍然有可执行的连线，是的
just because this is a dot water doesn't
仅仅因为这是点水就不会
mean you can't do Java - jar or rather
表示您无法使用Java-jar或更确切地说
Java - jar pointing to the del R so what
Java-指向del R的jar那么
I'm gonna do is I'm going to change the
我要做的就是我要改变
packaging on this where's my packaging
包装上这是我的包装
option to our and down here well I think
我认为我们的选择不错
it's it actually we need to add some
这是实际上我们需要添加一些
Java code we need to add a servlet
我们需要添加Java代码的servlet
initializer so I'll create a servlet
初始化程序，所以我将创建一个servlet
initializer we'll say okay create a new
初始化器，我们会说好的创建一个新的
one here initializer I'm gonna say that
一个初始化器，我要说
this extends spring boot servlet
这扩展了Spring Boot Servlet
initializer and the configure method we
初始化程序和configure方法
just need to point the configure method
只需要指出配置方法
to our our source so that's the servlet
到我们的资源，这就是servlet
demo application without the inner side
没有内侧的演示应用程序
line that's the actual Springwood entry
这是实际的Springwood条目
point that's where the public static
这就是公共静态的地方
void mean method is right so now with
void mean method是正确的，所以现在有了
that done I haven't gotten rid of this
做到了，我还没有摆脱这个
for a runtime just yet that's still
对于运行时而言，仍然
there right but now if I go to the
那里，但是现在如果我去
command line here CD sort of demo or in
命令行在这里CD演示或在
the Downloads demo directory downloads
Downloads演示目录下载
servlet demo directory here so if I go
servlet演示目录在这里，如果我去
back to my console I do
回到我的控制台
maven clean install we should get a dot
Maven的干净安装，我们应该得到一个点
War artifact as a result of the process
由于该过程而产生的战争神器
okay CD target I have a dot war I can
好的CD目标我可以打点战
now do Java - jar
现在做Java-jar
servlet demo lift out wha
servlet演示提升
okay and there we are there's the dot
好的，我们在那里
War artifact but it's still executive
战争神器，但仍在执行
because we still got the spring boot
因为我们还有 spring boot
maven plugin on the on the classpath now
现在在类路径上的Maven插件
it's technically not supported that you
从技术上讲，不支持您
deploy you know undertow into for
将您知道的知识部署到
example a wild fly applications or wild
例如野蝇应用程序或野外应用程序
fly is a redhead JBoss application
fly是一个红发的JBoss应用程序
server formerly known as JBoss AAS and
服务器以前称为JBoss AAS，
while undertow is the embedded servlet
而undertow是嵌入式servlet
container subsystem that's part of that
容器子系统的一部分
of that application server in the same
该应用程序服务器在同一位置
way you're not really supposed to deploy
您不应该真正部署的方式
Tomcat into Tomcat but most of them will
Tomcat转换为Tomcat，但其中大多数会
detect it and just kind of ignore it as
检测到它并以某种方式忽略它
opposed to to vetoing it right so I can
反对否决它，所以我可以
actually take this dot war which is a
实际上是参加这场点战
valid war and other and every other
有效战争及其他
respect except that it's got a public
尊重，除了它有一个公众
static void main and a runnable I can
静态void main和可运行的我可以
take that dot war and deploy it to an
进行点战争并将其部署到
actual undertow all right so let's see
实际知道了，所以让我们看看
servlet
小服务程序
dot war and I've got bin wildfly
点战，我有本·野蝇
standalone deployments right I've got
我拥有的独立部署
that I'm gonna put that in there and
我要把它放在那里
I'll run this as well now here's my
我也要运行这个，这是我的
standalone and wildfly application and
独立和Wildfly应用程序以及
you can see it's spinning up the
你会看到它在旋转
Springwood application there it is right
Springwood应用那里是正确的
there's our Springwood application here
这里有我们的Springwood应用程序
spring boot 1.52 can we see our NIT
spring boot 1.52我们可以看到我们的NIT吗
method is undertow right so there's that
方法是正确的所以有
as well my customizer and the
以及我的定制工具和
applications I've been running listening
我一直在监听的应用程序
on this port 9999 for management this is
在用于管理的此端口9999上是
the actual application here's the
实际的应用是
context so it's this thing that server
上下文，这就是服务器
demo snapshot you know localhost so
演示快照，你知道本地主机，所以
localhost 8080 greetings now there's our
本地主机8080问候现在是我们的
rest endpoint that's working as expected
其余端点正常工作
one thing that isn't gonna be working
一件事是行不通的
more than likely is for example our SSL
例如，我们的SSL更有可能
support or a compression or anything
支持或压缩或其他
that or the custom port anything that
该或自定义端口的任何
we'd specified in the Springwood
我们在Springwood中指定了
application here is a report
申请这里是一份报告
you know any of that stuff is not gonna
你知道那东西不会
work and the reason is because this
工作，原因是因为
we're now running inside of a runtime
我们现在在运行时内部运行
and that runtime doesn't let host or
并且该运行时不允许主机或
sorry
抱歉
guest applications control things like
来宾应用程序控制诸如
the application servers port and and you
应用程序服务器端口和您
know their connectors and and so on that
知道他们的连接器等等
are usually reserved for a separate rule
通常为单独的规则保留
in a traditional legacy application
在传统的遗留应用程序中
environment to configure right the
环境配置正确
developers out was to configure SSL
开发人员出来是要配置SSL
that's supposed to be done by somebody
那应该是有人做的
else before the idea of before the era
其他时代之前的想法
of sort of DevOps right when we had two
当我们有两个时
distinct rules between operations and
作业与
developers where they weren't sharing
他们不共享的开发者
the zone same codebase or
区域相同的代码库或
responsibilities and same goals so so
责任和相同的目标
that is not gonna work right these these
这些都行不通
properties are distinct features of the
属性是
embedded container you know ray runtime
您知道ray runtime的嵌入式容器
the embedded aspect of the spring good
弹簧的嵌入式方面很好
application okay so in this spring tip
应用程序还可以，所以在这个 spring 技巧 中
we've looked at how to deploy an
我们已经研究了如何部署
application how to deploy an application
应用程序如何部署应用程序
as an embedded jar as a sort of
作为嵌入式罐子
so-called fat jar and then how to turn
所谓的胖子罐子然后怎么转
it into a fatwa which you can deploy
它变成一个可以部署的法塔瓦
into a standard sort of application
进入标准的应用程序
server a Java EE application server this
服务器Java EE应用程序服务器
is just spring and spring boot and while
只是春天和 spring boot ，而
spring boot keeps a more cutting edge or
spring boot 保持更多的尖端或
up to date profile than then you're then
最新的个人资料，然后您
your everyday Spring Framework
您日常的Spring框架
application Spring Framework tends to
应用程序Spring Framework倾向于
have a longer backwards compatibility
向后兼容性更长
story this should still work on anything
故事这应该仍然适用于任何东西
of support strove it through that one
的支持力图通过那个
right so that's a fairly that goes back
对，所以这可以追溯到
to several years now it'll work just
到现在几年了
fine on on any of those containers that
对那些容器上的任何容器罚款
support that and servlets themselves are
支持这一点，并且servlet本身就是
a subset of Java Java EE so you don't
Java Java EE的子集，因此您不必
even need a java application server
甚至需要一个Java应用服务器
there's no reason you couldn't just
没有理由你不能只是
deploy this dot war into for example
例如，将这场点战部署到
Tomcat or Jenny or or whatever right
Tomcat或Jenny或其他权利
alright so thanks very much for watching
好，非常感谢您的收看
and we'll see you next time
下次再见
you
您